Hello everybody. I'm in the mood for
coffee, so let's go to a cafe together.
At this cafe, you can place your order
using a kiosk, so you don't even have to
talk to a barista here. Let's look at
the menu.
They even have an English option.
So convenient.
I usually like to eat in, but today I
have to go back to work, so I'll do
takeaway or takeout.
Usually in the mornings, I go for black
coffee, but in the afternoons, I like
something a little bit sweet. So, my
go-to drink is an ice latte.
I'm also trying to cut back on caffeine,
so I'll go for decaf.
A decaf vanilla latte sounds great.
Wow, it is so customizable here.
You can add an extra shot of espresso or
topping cream, which I'm guessing is
whipped cream.
I don't drink regular milk, so I'll
choose the non-dairy option, which is
oat milk.
And I'll add it to my cart.
I'm ready to pay, so I'll place my
order.
No, thank you. I'm all set.
So, this is my bill.
And I will pay with my husband's card.
So
This is a tip.
Um you can bring your husband's card.
I don't have a loyalty card here, so I
cannot earn points.
So I'll skip that. I'll pay with credit
card.
I'll scan my card.
I've got my receipt and my order number,
so I'll wait for my coffee to be
prepared. Korean cafes are the best.
They even have a photo zone at the cafe.
So I'll take a picture while I wait for
my coffee. They have props here, too.
How do I look? Cool?
I think I finished just in time. My
coffee is ready.
All right, looking good. Maybe I'll hang
it on the wall. I'll try not to cover
other people.
Ta-da!
Now I'll head to the counter to pick up
my coffee.
I've got my coffee and I'm going to use
a sleeve so my hands don't get too cold.
I'll also grab a straw.
And some cafes even have bottles of
syrup so you can pump extra sweetener
into your drink. This one doesn't have
it here. If you have more than one
drink, you can always ask for a carrier
as well. But I only have one coffee, so
I don't need a carrier today.
Now, it's the best part. I can finally
drink my coffee. So, I will take off the
lid
and stir the coffee and milk with my
straw. It's better when it's well mixed.
After mixing it, I'll put the lid back
on and take my first sip.
Mhm. Fire.
This is going to give me the energy I
need for work. Thank you, everybody, for
grabbing coffee with me today. If you
like this video, make sure to subscribe
to our channel, like, and let me know in
the comments where you want me to go
next. Thank you, everybody. Goodbye.